comeonengland.org 2018-08-01

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.  
Effective Date: May 1, 2010

1. **Introduction**   

> **General Introduction.** This privacy policy describes how this application collects and uses information collected through Facebook. Your information will only be used as described in this Privacy Policy; however, we may modify these policies from time to time.

 **2\. Types of Information Collected**

    1.  **Personal Information.** As our application operate within Facebook, the application may share information about you with others as may be necessary to operate the application.  For example, the social networking site may indicate to your friends that you have created a jersey. In order to send you updates and other information, you may wish to provide us with your email address. Providing your email to us is optional.
    2.  **Cookies.** In common with most web sites, we use standard technology called "cookies," which are small data files that are transferred to your computer when you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your Web browser to the application whenever you visit the application. Many improvements and updates to the application are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies also allows you to customize your experience on the application. If you do not want to allow information to be collected through the use of cookies, you can generally opt out of providing this information by turning the cookies off in your browser. However, some areas of the application may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.
    3.  **External Sites**. We are not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

3\. **Use of Information**

    1.  **Legal Compliance.**   
We release personal information only when we are required to do so in order to comply with the law.
    2.  **Advertising**.   
We do not sell or rent your information to any third party.

4\. **Security**

>  **Limits of Security Measures.**   
>  By using the application, you acknowledge that you understand that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet and that we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. ****** **

 **5\. Changes to this Polic** **y**

>  **Updates.** We reserve the right to change this policy at any time.  We will indicate material changes by posting the date of change at the top of this page.  
> 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of our application, you can contact us using the following email address: [support@gofansgo.com](mailto:webmaster@gofansgo.com)
